I'm still going to run with this base
case that the low will occur sometime
between now and like kind of between the
July to October window. When you look at
the year-to-date ROI of gold in midterm
years, and let's say look at 2026,
compare that to 2022, this is exactly
where gold was. It just feels worse this
time because we came from more elevated
levels, but this is where gold was.
In 2023, you can see gold started
trending back up again.
And in 2024, and in 2025, but the
midterm year was pretty weak. And in the
midterm year back then, gold bottomed in
late September of 2022. In 2018, gold
bottomed in about mid-August. And you
can also see that we're kind of lined up
with 2018 as well. And when you average
out 2018 and 2022, you can see that
we're right at the average of the last
two midterm years. And on average, they
bottomed in the August to September time
frame.